https://www.agilent.com/home/privacy-policy?elqTrackId=e7fe269c47af4c14aa469772c8874152&elqaid=568&elqat=2

AGILENT CUSTOMER PRIVACY STATEMENT
This Privacy Statement was last revised on 23 September 2020.
Agilent Technologies, Inc. and its subsidiaries (also referred to in this document as “Agilent Technologies”, “Agilent”, “we”, “our” and “us”) are committed to protecting and maintaining your privacy. Agilent Technologies, Inc. is established in the United States, with our registered office at 5301 Stevens Creek Boulevard, Santa Clara, CA 95051, United States and for the purpose of applicable laws, including but not limited to the General Data Protection Regulation (the “GDPR”) and the Brazilian General Data Protection Law (the “LGPD”), we are the data controller for all information processed in relation to the Website. The subsidiary you contract with will be the data controller of information provided for the purposes of marketing and providing any Agilent services. This privacy statement (“Privacy Statement”) is designed to make you aware of our privacy practices, of the types of information that we collect from you and how that information will be used both when you use our website and client portal at www.agilent.com (the “Website”) or interact with us offline in relation to providing or receiving goods and/or services. To make this notice easy to access, a link to it is available on the bottom of every Agilent web page.
If you wish to contact Agilent regarding your personal information or this Privacy Statement, please contact us at
data-protection.officer@agilent.com.
This Privacy Statement covers the collection, treatment and use of any personal information gathered by Agilent from customers, suppliers, vendors and other entities that Agilent does business with.
This Privacy Statement does not apply to the practices of third parties that we do not own or control, including but not limited to any third-party websites, services and applications that you elect to access through our Website.
If you do not agree with this Privacy Statement in general or any part of it, you should not access the Website. Please take a moment to review our policies and practices described below.
Throughout this Privacy Statement, “personal information” refers to any information that identifies you (either alone or together with other information) as an individual or relates to an identifiable individual, such as name, address, e-mail address, phone number, etc.
1. What Information We Collect
1.1 Customers and Vendors
During the course of your relationship with us, we collect personal information such as your name, postal address, telephone number, fax number, e-mail address, contact and billing information, transaction history (including order, lead, demo and service/repair history) and credit card or other financial information.
Through your in-person communications and/or online interactions with Agilent, we will ask you to provide information regarding your personal or professional interests, demographics, experience with our products and contact preferences. We will combine the information you provide to us through different communications and contact channels, such as combining data collected online with information provided offline. In addition, personal information will be required to determine access eligibility for certain restricted parts of our Website.
Further categories of information we collect are set out in Section 2 (How we use your personal information) below.
1.2 All visitors to Agilent websites
While you are visiting our Website, we may collect some technical data related to your browsing session such as IP address (we may also derive your approximate location from your IP address), browser type and language, number of visits to our Website and the hyperlinks you visited.
We use such technical data in aggregate form, as indicated in the paragraph below, without identifying you personally for Agilent’s own reporting, statistics and website enhancements, as well as for information security purposes.
Login or other tracking information that may identify you through website navigation will be stored for short time periods for technical security, website improvements, customer relationship purposes and so far as you continue interacting with Agilent.
Please see Section 8 (How we use cookies) below for our use of cookies and similar technologies.
2. How We Use Your Personal Information
Agilent will use the personal information that we collect from you for the purposes set out below. As it is in our legitimate interests to be responsive to you, to ensure the proper functioning of our products and organization and to provide you with a better service, we will use your personal information as follows.
We will use your contact and sign-in information such as your name, postal address, telephone number, fax number and e-mail address for the following purposes:
To communicate with you if you submit a query or request a quote.
To determine access eligibility for certain restricted parts of our Website.
To sign you up if you subscribe to receive our newsletter or content or if you sign up for our webinars.
We will also use your contact details and sign in information when you interact with our services divisions (such as the Diagnostics and Genomics Group (DGG), Agilent CrossLab Group (ACG) or Life Science and Applied Markets Group (LSAG)):
To provide the services to you, including providing quotes, proposals, demonstrations and generating contracts.
To provide customer services to you, including set-up and installation of products, processing and investigating complaints, providing professional services, training and certification.
To conduct research and development, provide quality assurance and product validation.
To process our regulatory filings in association with medical devices.
To comply with our regulatory requirements for compliance purposes.
To perform services and support on our products.
To improve our services and products.
To facilitate our annual conferences.
To provide a mail list, to facilitate a forum to discuss our products.
To provide marketing communications to you with your consent, improve our brand management and conduct market research.
For further detail on our data processing in relation to our services divisions, including information about the legal bases we rely on, please see here.
We will use your usage information, such as your IP address, browser type, number of visits to our Website and the hyperlinks for the following purposes:
To respond to technical or service problems;
To personalize our Website and communications;
To ensure content from our Website is presented in the most effective manner for you and your device;
To monitor and analyze trends, usage and activity in connection with our Website and to improve our Website;
To administer the Website and for internal operations, in order to conduct troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey analysis;
If applicable, to comply with local regulations;
To keep the Website safe and secure; and
To measure and understand the effectiveness of the content that we serve to you and others.
As part of the legal and regulatory obligations that we are subject to, we may also use your contact, usage and payment information to comply with such obligations and to comply with governmental and regulatory decisions.
We will use your personal information to better understand your needs and to provide you with a better service, including by responding to your correspondence, and providing updates on services and benefits.
Whenever we collect credit card numbers or other financial data, the data is only used for payment processing and the data is not retained for any other purpose.
From time to time in accordance with applicable law, we may also use your information to contact you for market research or to provide you with marketing information we think would be of particular interest. To unsubscribe from promotional emails, please click here or see Section 3 (Marketing Communications) below for more information.
User Forums
The Website may contain areas where users can transmit or post communications, for example on blogs, chat rooms, bulletin boards or user forums. You should be aware that any personal information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personal information you choose to submit in such public areas.
To find out further detail as to how we process personal data as part of our business lines, learn more here. learn more here.
Why we collect your data
Categories of personal data
Legal basis for processing
Retention period*
Marketing communications including newsletters, webinars, and direct marketing.
To help us personalize and improve your Agilent experience, we collect certain information when you connect with us, including when you:
Register on Agilent.com
Subscribe or Unsubscribe from Agilent marketing emails and newsletters
Attend an Agilent webinar, seminar and other Agilent hosted events
Participate in Agilent promotions and sweepstakes
Request information about Agilent products and services.
Name, title and contact details including email address and telephone number.
Consent – we obtain opt in consent before marketing to contacts where required by applicable law.
Legitimate interests of marketing to new and existing customers.
5 years.
After five years Agilent will request your confirmation to continue to receive marketing communications.
Presales activities including provision of quotes, proposals, customer demos, producing contracts.
Name, title and contact details including email address and telephone number.
Legitimate interests of selling products and services to new and existing customers.
20 years from expiration of customer agreement, due to the lifespan of Agilent products.
Sale of goods and services
Name, title, contact details including email address and telephone number
Financial information including bank account information
Legitimate interests of selling products and services to new and existing customers
20 years from when we sold you goods or provided services due to the lifespan of Agilent products.
Customer services including complaint investigation and compliance activities.
Provision of professional services including certification and training for clinical trials, support, training.
Name, title and contact details including email address and telephone number.
Legitimate interests of supporting existing customers.
Compliance with legal and regulatory obligations.
Service and support records are retained for 20 years post expiration of the customer agreement except where specific Product Line retention periods apply – please refer to your Customer contract.
Records related to product installation/associated training are kept from the date of install for 20 years.
Records related to complaints and compliance activities are retained in line with our obligations for regulated devices (e.g. by the FDA) and other regulatory and legal requirements, for 10 years after the expiry of the product in question.
Research and development (“R&D”), quality assurance, product validation (product testing pre-sales).
Name, title and contact details including email address and telephone number.
Legitimate interests in testing, evaluating and improving Agilent products and services.
Records relating to R&D for new products are maintained until such time as they are no longer required for R&D purposes.
Clinical trial studies and associated regulatory filings.
Name, title and contact details including email address and telephone number of Pharma Partners and their affiliated and/or contracted lab staff.
Qualifications and educational background information including, curriculum vitae information, medical licenses, registrations and any board certifications of Clinical Lab Staff working on Clinical Trials.
Financial information including Financial Disclosure (FD) forms which lists the individual Clinical Lab Staff Member and any of their immediate family members who may have an investment in Agilent or the Pharma Partner involved in the trial.
Key-coded health data, including pseudonymized, patient IDs are provided to Agilent with no ability to re-identify the individual Clinical Trial Participant.
When performing Clinical Trial Surveillance or Monitoring on behalf of a Clinical Trial Sponsor, the Sponsor acts as the data controller of such data, and Agilent as a data processor.
Pseudonymized, patient IDs are collected by the Sponsors of the Clinical Trial. Agilent receives this information only to fulfill Agilent’s legal obligations in regard to regulatory filings.
Clinical trials data are kept for as long as the agreement is in place with the Clinical Trial Sponsor + 5 years minimum per FDA guidance.
Records associated with US regulatory approval will be kept indefinitely in line with FDA standards.
For any other Clinical Trials data, this would fall under the 5 year retention period (post agreement with a Clinical Trial Sponsor).
Installation and access to product platforms.
Name, title and contact details including email address and telephone number.
Legitimate interest to provide individual access to Agilent’s product platforms.
20 years from the date of installation.
Customer experience surveys and market research interviews.
Name, title and contact details including email address and telephone number.
Consent – we obtain opt in consent before sending customer experience surveys to contacts where required by applicable law.
Consent – we obtain opt-in consent before asking you to participate in market research interviews, where required by applicable law.
Legitimate interests of marketing to new and existing customers.
Customer experience survey data is kept for 20 years.
To facilitate conferences and events for customers where Agilent advertises new features, updates, product road maps.
Name, title and contact details including email address and telephone number.
Employment information related to where a conference attendee is currently employed.
NOTE: Financial information, including transaction and credit card details used to pay for conference attendance may be collected by a third party managing a conference event but Agilent does not process such data directly.
Legitimate interests of marketing to new and existing customers.
5 years.
After five years Agilent will request your confirmation to continue to receive marketing communications.
Customer listServ (mail list) and user forums to discuss products and services.
Name, title and contact details including email address and telephone number.
Employment information related to where a Listserv or forum contributor is employed.
Consent to participate in the mail list or user forum mail list.
Legitimate interests of processing forum data to sell products and services to new and existing customers.
User data is kept until opt out of the listserv/mail list or forum
Procurement of goods and services
Name, title and contact details including email address and telephone number.
Legitimate interests in purchasing goods and services in Agilent.
30 years after the vendor relationship ends.
*Individual retention periods may apply to specific product lines. Please refer to the terms and conditions of the product.
We note that in several of our divisions, we process personal data as a data processor when providing these services. We process such data on our client’s instructions and in accordance with the terms of our services agreements and customer contracts.
3. Marketing Communications
To the extent permitted by applicable laws (including only with your consent where required by applicable laws), we will send you periodic marketing messages from Agilent, including newsletters, promotions and special offers. We will use your name, postal address, telephone number, fax number, social media profile and email address to send these messages to you. You are able to opt out of receiving such messages without any negative effect to your relationship with Agilent by following the unsubscribe instructions included within this Privacy Statement and included in each marketing email. Please keep in mind that if you choose not to receive these promotional emails, you will continue to receive emails from Agilent about recent transactions, including request for quotes, purchases and software updates. We also reserve the right to contact you when we believe it necessary, including where required by law.
The choice to opt out of promotional emails will be offered at the bottom of our online or offline communications to you as well as on our web registration pages.
If you have any difficulty opting out, please use this unsubscribe form.
4. Where We Store and Who We Share Your Personal Information With
The personal information that we collect from you in relation to the provision of our Website will be transferred to, and processed in the USA by Agilent Technologies, Inc. so that we can perform our contractual obligations with you.
The personal information that we collect from you in relation to the selling of our products and services will be subject to the terms of the local Agilent subsidiary you contract with. Where the GDPR applies, such personal information will be transferred to, and processed in the USA by Agilent Technologies, Inc. under the European Commission’s model contracts for the transfer of personal data to third countries (i.e., the standard contractual clauses) (the “Model Clauses”), pursuant to Decision 2004/915/EC and 2010/87/EU. Please contact data-protection.officer@agilent.com, if you would like to see a copy of the Model Clauses. Where the LGPD applies, Agilent will rely on the lawful basis of performance of a contract to transfer personal data outside of Brazil, including to the United States, as well as implement further mechanisms for the safety of these international transfers, as required by the Brazilian Data Protection Authority.
In addition to the above, Agilent’s global organizational structure also requires the global transfer of personal information within the Agilent group of companies. As a consequence, as it is in our legitimate interests for the efficient operation of a global company, and as permitted by applicable law,
the personal information that you provide to us will be transferred across state or country borders, including to countries outside the country in which you reside (including to countries outside the EEA and outside of Brazil), to consolidate data storage, simplify information management or synchronize information on customer relationship activities globally. It will also be processed by staff operating outside the country in which you reside (including countries outside of the EEA and outside of Brazil) who work for us or one of our resellers, distributors, service providers or suppliers as noted below.
We share your information with selected recipients. These categories of recipients include:
Cloud storage providers to store the personal information you provide and for disaster recovery services;
Service providers that provide us with customer relationship management services;
Services providers that provide us with survey services;
Service providers that provide us with market research and digital marketing services;
Agents and suppliers that provide us with technology services;
Authorized service providers for field service engineering;
Distributors of our products and services;
Sales management services providers that provide us with SaaS services;
Services providers including that provide us with invoicing services; and
Our professional advisors, auditors and business partners;
Support providers to provide customer support services.
Where the GDPR applies and the recipient of your personal information is located outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”), such transfer will either be: (i) to a recipient under their approved Binding Corporate Rules; or (ii) subject to the Model Clauses.
Agilent will also disclose your personal information: (i) if we are required to do so by law – for example, in certain circumstances, courts, law enforcement agencies, regulatory agencies or security authorities in other countries, including the U.S., may be entitled to access your personal information.;(ii) if we believe that it is necessary to enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements or otherwise protect and defend the rights, property or safety of Agilent or that of our customers; (iii) in order to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order or other legal obligation or government inquiry; or (iv) to any entity that acquires any part of Agilent’s current operations by way of merger, de-merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Website of any change in ownership or usage of your personal information, as well as any choices you have regarding your personal information.
5. How long We Store Your Personal Information For
We will retain your personal information in accordance with the retention periods set out in the tables above in Section 1 (What information we collect),
here
here
Why we collect your data
Categories of personal data
Legal basis for processing
Retention period*
Marketing communications including newsletters, webinars, and direct marketing.
To help us personalize and improve your Agilent experience, we collect certain information when you connect with us, including when you:
Register on Agilent.com
Subscribe or Unsubscribe from Agilent marketing emails and newsletters
Attend an Agilent webinar, seminar and other Agilent hosted events
Participate in Agilent promotions and sweepstakes
Request information about Agilent products and services.
Name, title and contact details including email address and telephone number.
Consent – we obtain opt in consent before marketing to contacts where required by applicable law.
Legitimate interests of marketing to new and existing customers.
5 years.
After five years Agilent will request your confirmation to continue to receive marketing communications.
Presales activities including provision of quotes, proposals, customer demos, producing contracts.
Name, title and contact details including email address and telephone number.
Legitimate interests of selling products and services to new and existing customers.
20 years from expiration of customer agreement, due to the lifespan of Agilent products.
Sale of goods and services
Name, title, contact details including email address and telephone number
Financial information including bank account information
Legitimate interests of selling products and services to new and existing customers
20 years from when we sold you goods or provided services due to the lifespan of Agilent products.
Customer services including complaint investigation and compliance activities.
Provision of professional services including certification and training for clinical trials, support, training.
Name, title and contact details including email address and telephone number.
Legitimate interests of supporting existing customers.
Compliance with legal and regulatory obligations.
Service and support records are retained for 20 years post expiration of the customer agreement except where specific Product Line retention periods apply – please refer to your Customer contract.
Records related to product installation/associated training are kept from the date of install for 20 years.
Records related to complaints and compliance activities are retained in line with our obligations for regulated devices (e.g. by the FDA) and other regulatory and legal requirements, for 10 years after the expiry of the product in question.
Research and development (“R&D”), quality assurance, product validation (product testing pre-sales).
Name, title and contact details including email address and telephone number.
Legitimate interests in testing, evaluating and improving Agilent products and services.
Records relating to R&D for new products are maintained until such time as they are no longer required for R&D purposes.
Clinical trial studies and associated regulatory filings.
Name, title and contact details including email address and telephone number of Pharma Partners and their affiliated and/or contracted lab staff.
Qualifications and educational background information including, curriculum vitae information, medical licenses, registrations and any board certifications of Clinical Lab Staff working on Clinical Trials.
Financial information including Financial Disclosure (FD) forms which lists the individual Clinical Lab Staff Member and any of their immediate family members who may have an investment in Agilent or the Pharma Partner involved in the trial.
Key-coded health data, including pseudonymized, patient IDs are provided to Agilent with no ability to re-identify the individual Clinical Trial Participant.
When performing Clinical Trial Surveillance or Monitoring on behalf of a Clinical Trial Sponsor, the Sponsor acts as the data controller of such data, and Agilent as a data processor.
Pseudonymized, patient IDs are collected by the Sponsors of the Clinical Trial. Agilent receives this information only to fulfill Agilent’s legal obligations in regard to regulatory filings.
Clinical trials data are kept for as long as the agreement is in place with the Clinical Trial Sponsor + 5 years minimum per FDA guidance.
Records associated with US regulatory approval will be kept indefinitely in line with FDA standards.
For any other Clinical Trials data, this would fall under the 5 year retention period (post agreement with a Clinical Trial Sponsor).
Installation and access to product platforms.
Name, title and contact details including email address and telephone number.
Legitimate interest to provide individual access to Agilent’s product platforms.
20 years from the date of installation.
Customer experience surveys and market research interviews.
Name, title and contact details including email address and telephone number.
Consent – we obtain opt in consent before sending customer experience surveys to contacts where required by applicable law.
Consent – we obtain opt-in consent before asking you to participate in market research interviews, where required by applicable law.
Legitimate interests of marketing to new and existing customers.
Customer experience survey data is kept for 20 years.
To facilitate conferences and events for customers where Agilent advertises new features, updates, product road maps.
Name, title and contact details including email address and telephone number.
Employment information related to where a conference attendee is currently employed.
NOTE: Financial information, including transaction and credit card details used to pay for conference attendance may be collected by a third party managing a conference event but Agilent does not process such data directly.
Legitimate interests of marketing to new and existing customers.
5 years.
After five years Agilent will request your confirmation to continue to receive marketing communications.
Customer listServ (mail list) and user forums to discuss products and services.
Name, title and contact details including email address and telephone number.
Employment information related to where a Listserv or forum contributor is employed.
Consent to participate in the mail list or user forum mail list.
Legitimate interests of processing forum data to sell products and services to new and existing customers.
User data is kept until opt out of the listserv/mail list or forum
Procurement of goods and services
Name, title and contact details including email address and telephone number.
Legitimate interests in purchasing goods and services in Agilent.
30 years after the vendor relationship ends.
*Individual retention periods may apply to specific product lines. Please refer to the terms and conditions of the product.
6. YOUR RIGHTS
Under applicable law, including where GDPR and the LGPD applies, you have the following rights.
Your rights under the GDPR:
Access and Portability: You have the right to ask us to access the personal data we hold about you and be provided with certain information about how we use your personal data and who we share it with.
Where GDPR applies, when you have provided your personal data to us with your consent, you have the right to ask us for a copy of this data in a structured, machine readable format and to ask us to share (port) this data to another data controller.
You can withdraw your consent at any time by clicking here.
Correction: You also have the right to ask us to correct your personal data where it is inaccurate or incomplete.
Right to deletion: In certain circumstances, you have the right to ask us to delete the personal data we hold about you. Find out further information about your right to delete here here
where you believe that it is no longer necessary for us to hold your personal data;
where we are processing your personal data on the basis of legitimate interests and you object to such processing and we cannot demonstrate an overriding legitimate ground for the processing;
where you have provided your personal data to us with your consent and you wish to withdraw your consent and there is no other ground under which we can process your personal data; or
where you believe the personal data we hold about you is being unlawfully processed by us.
Restriction: In certain circumstances, you have the right to ask us to restrict (stop any active) processing of your personal data. Find out further information about your ability to restrict data processing here here
where you believe the personal data we hold about you is inaccurate and while we verify accuracy;
where we want to erase your personal data as the processing is unlawful but you want us to continue to store it;
where we no longer need your personal data for the purposes of our processing but you require us to retain the data for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims; or
where you have objected to us processing your personal data based on our legitimate interests and we are considering your objection.
Objection: Where GDPR applies, you can object to our processing of your personal data based on our legitimate interests and we will no longer process your personal data unless we can demonstrate an overriding legitimate ground.
Your rights under the LGPD:
Confirmation, Access and Portability:
You have the right to ask us to access the personal data we hold about you and be provided with certain information about how we use your personal data and who we share it with.
Where LGPD applies, Agilent allows the user or third parties indicated by the user to access the personal data processed by Agilent in structured, inter-operable format.
Not to provide consent or withdraw consent: The user has the right not to provide or to withdraw his or her consent, however, such fact will not affect the legality of any processing previously carried out. If the user does not supply or revokes its consent, perhaps Agilent may not be able to provide certain products and services. When this is the case, Agilent will let you know.
You can withdraw your consent at any time by clicking here.
Correction: You also have the right to ask us to correct your personal data where it is inaccurate or incomplete.
Right to deletion, blockage or anonymization:: In certain circumstances, you have the right to ask us to delete, block or anonymize the personal data we hold about you.
Restriction: In certain circumstances, you have the right to ask us to restrict (stop any active) processing of your personal data.
Objection: Where LGPD applies, you are entitled to object for specific processing purposes. In some cases, Agilent may demonstrate it has legitimate reasons to process your personal data, which may override your rights, if, for instance, they are strictly essential for the functionality of the products or services.
To exercise any of these rights above, please click here. In addition, you have the right to complain to any applicable data protection supervisory authority.
Please note that these rights might be limited, for example, where fulfilling your request would adversely affect other individuals or company trade secrets or intellectual property, where there are overriding public interest reasons or where we are required by law to retain your personal data.
At any time, you have the right to object to our processing of data about you in order to send you marketing, including where we build profiles for such purposes, and we will stop processing the data for that purpose.
In the event that you wish to make a complaint about how we process your personal information, please contact us in the first instance at data-protection.officer@agilent.com and we will endeavor to deal with your request as soon as possible. This is without prejudice to your right to raise a complaint with a relevant supervisory authority in the country in which you live or work, where you think we have infringed data protection laws.
7. How We Keep Your Personal Information Secure
Agilent is committed to ensuring the security of your personal information. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of personal information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic and organizational measures to safeguard and secure it. For information on Agilent’s approach to information security please visit this link.
Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share this password with anyone.
Unfortunately, the transmission of information over the internet is not completely secure. We cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our Website; any transmission is at your own risk.
If you have any questions about security on our Website, please visit.
8. How We Use Cookies
While you are visiting our Website, we collect technical data related to your browsing session such as IP address, approximate geolocation based on IP address information, browser type and language, number of visits to our Website and the hyperlinks you visited.
We use such technical data in aggregate form without identifying you personally for Agilent’s own reporting, statistics and website enhancements, as well as for information security purposes. In addition, we use individual IP address information to derive the approximate geolocation of our users and deliver the most relevant content, and in other circumstances to direct you to the appropriate customer service/chat agent. We may have the ability to link an individual IP address to you as a customer if you have also provided us with your information while registering on Agilent.com or otherwise filling out various product, promotional and other forms on this Website.
For further details about the data we collect through cookies, their purpose and your choices in relation to cookies, please see here
see here
Types of Data Collected Through Cookies and Purposes of Cookies’ Use
Agilent uses technologies, such as web-tracking tools designed for website session analysis and profiling of the users of our Website. Such technologies enable us to optimize our Website content and tailor it and other communications to you.
A cookie is a text file containing small amounts of information stored on your computer’s hard drive when you visit a webpage. Session cookies are erased when the user closes the web browser or browser tab. Persistent cookies remain on your hard drive until they expire or are deleted. Cookies will also be set by third parties operating on our behalf (e.g. to help us analyze web traffic or to improve your web navigation experience).
Some cookies are necessary for our website’s functionality and enable you to place an item in our online cart and to place an order on our website. Other cookies allow us to enhance and personalize your Agilent.com web browsing experience, so the information you receive is more relevant to you. Here are some examples of what cookies allow us to do:
Remember what items are in your online cart;
Recognize when you return to our website;
Enable faster checkout and remember what you ordered if you have created an account on Agilent.com;
Analyze how our customers navigate our website and which products they search for; and
Deliver personalized marketing from Agilent.
If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, most browsers allow you to automatically decline cookies or be given the choice of declining or accepting a particular cookie (or cookies) from a particular website. You can find more information about cookies and how to manage them at http://www.allaboutcookies.org/. If you set your browser to refuse all cookies, please contact us directly to place your order.
Cookie. Clear Gif. Tag and Script Usage and Your Choices About Tracking Technologies
We use the following types of cookies on our Website to help us analyze web traffic, to improve your web experience and to better target our marketing of products and services:
Strictly necessary cookies, which are essential in order to enable you to move around the website and use its features.
Performance cookies, which collect information about how you use the website, for instance which pages you visit most often.
Functionality cookies, which allow the website to remember choices you make (e.g. remembering your user name, language or the region you are in) and provide enhanced, more personal features.
Advertising cookies, which are used to deliver advertisements more relevant to you and your interests. They are also used to limit the number of times you see an advertisement as well as help measure the effectiveness of the advertising campaign.
In addition, we may use Flash LSOs and other technologies to, among other things, collect and store information about your use of the Website. If you do not want Flash LSOs stored on your computer, you can adjust the settings of your Flash player to block Flash LSO storage using the tools contained in the Website Storage Settings Panel. You can also go to the Global Storage Settings Panel and follow the instructions (which may explain, for example, how to delete existing Flash LSOs (referred to as “information”), how to prevent Flash LSOs from being placed on your computer without your being asked, and how to block Flash LSOs that are not being delivered by the operator of the page you are on at the time). Please note that setting the Flash Player to restrict or limit acceptance of Flash LSOs may reduce or impede the functionality of some Flash applications.
To facilitate the analysis of web traffic, an ID is assigned to help us uniquely identify you each time you return to our Website.
By gathering and remembering information about your website preferences through cookies we can provide a better web and marketing experience. Specifically, cookies enable us to:
Tailor our Website’s operation to your needs, likes and dislikes.
Provide an automated log-in process as a convenience for previously registered customers, ensuring that you will be identified accurately and linked with your registration data.
Ensure you are not surveyed multiple times during your visit(s) to an Agilent website.
Provide a better web experience by letting us monitor what is working and what is not.
We also partner with third party ad networks to either display advertising on our Website or to manage our advertising on other sites.
You may receive advertisements based on information relating to your access to and use of the Website and other websites or online services on any of your devices, as well as on information received from third parties.
Our ad network partners place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser, including through the use of pixel tags.
They also use these technologies, along with information they collect about your online use, to recognize you across the devices you use, such as a mobile phone and a laptop.
If you would like more information about this practice, and to learn how to opt out of it in desktop and mobile browsers on the particular device on which you are accessing this Privacy Statement, please visit https://optout.aboutads.info/#/ and https://optout.networkadvertising.org/#/. Or if you are located in the European Union, click here. Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.
As a user you have the ability to accept or decline the use of cookies. Where required by law, Agilent indicates its use of cookies through a prominent banner on our Website. Cookies can be removed explicitly using functionality built into most web browsers and you can refuse to accept cookies by activating this setting on your browser. You can also set up your web browser to notify you of cookie placement requests, to ask for permission to accept them, or to decline cookies completely. For information on how to adjust your browser regarding cookies, please visit:
Microsoft Internet Explorer:
https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies#ie=ie-11 Firefox: https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/block-websites-storing-cookies-site-data-firefox Chrome: https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en Safari: https://support.apple.com/guide/safari/manage-cookies-and-website-data-sfri11471/mac Opera: https://www.opera.com/browser/tutorials/security/
If you choose to decline cookies, parts of the Website will be unavailable to you.
Log Files
As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information will include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data. We use this information to improve services we offer you, analytics and site functionality and also to comply with legal obligations, where applicable. We do not use this data for any other purpose.
Technologies such as: cookies (as detailed above), clear gifs, tags and scripts are used by us and our analytics companies Google Analytics and Eloqua. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We will receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis. We also will use Clear Gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. For this reason, Clear Gifs will be tied to your personal information.
Website Tracking
We use Google Analytics and Eloqua, which are web analytics tools, to help us understand how users engage with our Website. Like many services, Google Analytics and Eloqua track your movement through our site (i.e. the pages you have seen and the links you have clicked on) and help us measure how you interact with the content that we provide. This information is used to compile reports and to help us improve our Website. The reports disclose website trends without identifying individual visitors. You can learn about Google’s practices by going to www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/, and exercise the opt-out provided by Google by downloading the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on, available at https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
You can opt out of accepting cookies, but this will affect your personalized experience of Agilent.com.
For further details about the data we collect through cookies, their purpose and your choices in relation to cookies, please see here.
Cookie Settings
9. Additional Information
Links to Third-Party Websites
Links to third-party websites are provided solely as a convenience to you. If you use these links, you will leave the Agilent Website. Agilent has not reviewed, does not control and is not responsible for these websites, their content or their privacy statement. Thus, we do not endorse or make any representations about them, any information, software or other products or materials found there, or any results of using them. If you decide to access any of the third-party sites linked to Agilent’s website, you do so entirely at your own risk and acknowledge that there might be risks that are not controlled or otherwise related to Agilent’s activities.
Use of the Website by Minors
The Website is not directed to individuals under the age of sixteen (16), and we do not knowingly collect personal information from individuals under 16.
Jobs@Agilent
When you choose to post a resume to our Website and apply to become part of the Agilent team, please note that you will be taken to a third-party URL (here) and these pages will be branded as Agilent. The information you provide via the URL will be used solely for the purposes for which it is provided (including the processing of your application) and will be retained for such period as is necessary to comply with Agilent’s legal and administrative requirements. The information collected and used while on these hosted pages is subject to the following sections of this Privacy Statement to the extent applicable to resumes: How We use Cookies; Who we share your personal information with; How long we store your personal information for; and How we keep your personal information secure.
For further information, please refer to our Candidate Privacy Notice which provides information about how Agilent uses your personal information.
Email a Page
If you choose to use our Email a Page service, your name, comments and the email addresses you provide will not be used for any other purpose than to complete this page-forwarding transaction.
Changes to the Privacy Statement
This Privacy Statement is effective as of the date stated at the start of this Privacy Statement. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Statement at any time by posting the revised policy on our Website and updating the date the statement was last revised at the start of this Privacy Statement, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this Privacy Statement, we will notify you by email or by means of a prominent notice on our home page.
Contact Information
Please send/contact us with questions or comments about our privacy practices at:
Data Protection Officer at data-protection.officer@agilent.com
Agilent Technologies, Inc.5301 Stevens Creek Blvd.Santa Clara, CA 95051USA
Phone: (408) 553 -4417
Additional Information for Nevada Residents
We do not sell Covered Information as defined under Nevada law. If you would like to make any inquiry regarding the sale of your Covered Information, please contact data-protection.officer@agilent.com that has been designated for privacy inquiries by Nevada residents.
Additional Information for California Residents
Pursuant to the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (“CCPA”), we are providing the following additional details regarding the categories of Personal Information about California residents that we have collected (online and offline) or disclosed within the preceding 12 months.
This CCPA Addendum does not apply to our job applicants, employees, contractors, owners, directors, or officers where the Personal Information we collect about those individuals relates to their current, former, or potential role with us.
Under the CCPA, “Personal Information” is information that identifies, relates to, or could reasonably be linked with a particular California resident or household.
We collected the following categories of Personal Information:
Identifiers, such as name, contact information, IP address and other online identifiers;
Personal information, as defined in the California customer records law, such as name, and contact information;
Characteristics of protected classifications under California or federal law, such as gender;
Commercial information, such as transaction information and purchase history;
Internet or network activity information, such as browsing history and interactions with our website;
Geolocation data, such as approximate location based on IP address information;
Audio, electronic, visual, and similar information, such as call recordings; and
Professional or employment-related information, such as current employer.
We collect this Personal Information from you as well as from our affiliates, publicly available databases, event co-sponsors, joint marketing partners and our distributors/resellers.
We use this Personal Information to operate, manage, and maintain our business, to provide our products and services, and to accomplish our business purposes and objectives, as described above in this Privacy Statement under “How We Use Your Personal Information.”
We disclosed the following Personal Information to third parties for our operational business purposes:
Identifiers, such as name, contact information, IP address and other online identifiers;
Personal information, as defined in the California customer records law, such as name, and contact information;
Characteristics of protected classifications under California or federal law, such as gender;
Commercial information, such as transaction information and purchase history;
Internet or network activity information, such as browsing history and interactions with our website;
Geolocation data, such as approximate location based on IP address information;
Audio, electronic, visual, and similar information, such as call recordings; and
Professional or employment-related information, such as current employer;
We disclosed these categories of Personal Information to: our affiliates; resellers and distributors; agents, suppliers, and other trusted third-party service providers; and our professional advisors, auditors and business partners.
We have not “sold” Personal Information for purposes of the CCPA/“sold” the following categories of Personal Information:
Identifiers, such as name, contact information, IP address and other online identifiers;
Personal information, as defined in the California customer records law, such as name and contact information;
Characteristics of protected classifications under California or federal law, such as gender;
Commercial information, such as transaction information and purchase history;
Internet or network activity information, such as browsing history and interactions with our website;
Geolocation data, such as approximate location based on IP address information;
Audio, electronic, visual, and similar information, such as call recordings; or
Professional or employment-related information, such as current employer.
For purposes of this Privacy Statement, “sold” or “sale” means the disclosure of Personal Information for monetary or other valuable consideration but does not include, for example, the transfer of Personal Information as an asset that is part of a merger, bankruptcy, or other disposition of all or any portion of our business.
If you are a California resident, you may request that we:
Disclose to you the following information covering the 12 months preceding your request:
The categories of Personal Information we collected about you and the categories of sources from which we collected such Personal Information;
The specific pieces of Personal Information we collected about you;
The business or commercial purpose for collecting Personal Information about you;
The categories of Personal Information about you that we sold and the categories of third parties to whom we sold such Personal Information (if applicable);
The categories of Personal Information about you that we otherwise shared or disclosed, and the categories of third parties with whom we shared or to whom we disclosed such Personal Information (if applicable).
Delete Personal Information we collected from you.
To make a request for the disclosures or deletion described above, please contact us here or at +1-800-227-9770. We will respond to your request consistent with applicable law.
You have the right to be free from unlawful discrimination for exercising your rights under the CCPA.
